A Guide to the Papers of Dr. Edward Watson Hook, Jr., 1947-1998
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- SERIES 4: Office Files, alphabetically arranged
  - MAAP II: Humanities in Medicine, 1998 June 1998, 1 TMs, 1 TD (Box-folder 030-014)
    Re: Course syllabus for Humanities in Medicine.
  - MAAP; Student Essays Summer 1998, 1 TMs (Box-folder 030-015)
    Re: Student Essays: "What the Doctor Said, What the Doctor Did: Student Essays About Role Models for Medicine".
  - MAAP II June 1997, 1 TD, 1 article, 1 AD (Box-folder 030-016)
    Re: Course syllabus for Hook's June 1997 MAAP class.
  - Medical Clinics June 1986-June 1990, 6 TMemo, 42 TLS, 1 Graph, 12 TD, 1 ALS (Box-folder 031-001)
    Re: Hook established two advisory committees for the Medical Subspecialty Clinic, included are correspondence with committee members and meeting minutes.
  - MIS (Medical Information Service) August 1988-April 1990, 27 TLS, 4 TMemo, 2 TD, 1 TMs, 1 TL (Box-folder 031-002)
    Re: Patient care, pharmaceutical procedures, and MIS problems, deficiencies, and negotiations.
  - Medical Intensive Care Unit April 1975-May 1983, 24 TLS, 3 TMemo, 2 TD, 1 Map, 6 TL, 1 AN (Box-folder 031-003)
    Re: Amount of beds needed, space assignments, nursing care, and utilization of MICU.
  - Medical Intensive Care Unit (Cont.) January 1984-March 1990, 40 TLS, 4 TMemo, 2 TD, 2 TL, 1 Map (Box-folder 031-00)
    Re: Nursing coverage, patient care, and utilization of MICU beds.
  - Medical Records, completion of March 1987-November 1989, 8 TLS, 1 TN, 1 TMemo, 1 TMs (Box-folder 031-005)
    Re: Includes a 1987 manuscript, "Medical Record Completion Policy".
  - Medical Correspondence, 1982-present November 1984-April 1990, 20 TLS, 3 TMemo, 1 TD, 3 Newspaper clippings (photocopies) (Box-folder 031-006)
    Re: Correspondence is primarily about medicare.
  - Associate Chairman for Clinical Affairs June 1989-June 1990, 9 TLS, 2 TMemo (Box-folder 031-007)
    Re: Utilization of clinics and need for ambulatory space.
  - Associate Chairman for Education June-December 1989, 7 TLS (Box-folder 031-008)
    Re: Correspondence with Gerald R. Donowitz about clerkships and rotation of third-year students.
  - Associate Chairman for Research August 1989-March 1990, 6 TLS, 1 TMemo, 1 TD (Box-folder 031-009)
    Re: Nutrition space, postgraduate medical scientist training program, proposal for voluntary departmental critique service, and faculty research index.
  - Associate Chairman for Residency Program June 1989-May 1990, 23 TLS, 2 TMemo, 2 TD (Box-folder 031-010)
    Re: Hook delves into patient care by residents and resident positions.
  - Department of-Attending Rounds February 1982-April 1990, 5 TMemo, 1 TMs, 10 TLS, 3 TD, 1 AD (Box-folder 031-011)
    Re: Includes "Guidelines for Attending Physicians in Internal Medicine", 1982 and a revised 1990 version, and results from a questionnaire on Inpatient Teaching.
  - Medicine, Binennial 1988, 1 TMs (Box-folder 031-012)
    Re: Hook chaired the 1986-1988 "Biennial Evaluation and Planning Report Department of Medicine".
  - Medicine, Department of Billing February 1981-June 1990, 19 TLS, 1 TL, 8 TD, 2 TMemo, 1 TNS (Box-folder 032-001)
    Re: Billing problems, 1981 "Memorandum of Understanding," raising of professional fees, and after hours services billing difficulties.
  - Medicine, Department of-correspondence March 1970-March 1977, 64 TMemo, 6 TD, 4 TLS, 1 TL, 1 Article (Box-folder 032-002)
    Re: Correspondence with division heads: scheduling of meetings and yearly divisional structure of the department of Medicine.
  - Division Heads Retreat December 1987-March 1988, 5 TMemo, 6 TLS, 2 TD (Box-folder 032-003)
    Re: Items relating to February 22, 1988 division head retreat.
  - Medicine, Department of-faculty December 1982-March 1989, 1 TL, 8 TLS, 6 TMemo, 2 TD (Box-folder 032-004)
    Re: Faculty salaries, residents, & recruitment of minority faculty.
  - Medicine, Department of-Five-Year Projections December 15, 1981, 1 TLS, 1 TMs (Box-folder 032-005)
    Re: Manuscript projects inpatient & outpatient services and program expansion and new program development for the UVa Hospital.
  - Medicine, Department of Finance 1989 April 1984-April 1990, 40 TLS, 14 TMemo, 9 TD, 1 TMs, 1 Newspaper article (photocopy) (Box-folder 032-006)
    Re: Audits, increase in salaries, department contributing 15%, billing, budgets, overhead funds, and payment of facilities.
  - Medicine, Department of-Friends of the Department January 1983-September 1984, 1 TMemo, 1 TD, 6 TLS (Box-folder 032-007)
    Re: Includes speech by Hook to Friends of the Department.
  - Medicine, Department-Meeting Minutes June-December 1989, 21 TD, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 032-008)
    Re: Hook chaired meetings.
  - Medicine, Department-Meeting Minutes January-December 1990, 49 TD (Box-folder 032-009)
    Re: Hook chaired some of the meetings.
  - Medicine, Department-New & Expanded Programs 1987-1988 [n.d.], 10 TMs, 16 TD, 6 TMemo, 2 TLS, 1 TN (Box-folder 032-010)
    Re: Proposals from Division Heads in Internal Medicine for new or expanded programs to be considered for funding by the Financial Planning Committee.
  - Medicine, Department of-Professional Liability Policy January 1973-February 1987, 2 TMemo, 3 TLS (Box-folder 032-011)
    Re: Hook's correspondence regarding medical malpractice insurance.
  - Medicine, Department of-Research Institutes & Centers September-November 1986, 2 TMemo, 1 TLS (Box-folder 032-012)
    Re: Department meeting about creation of major research institute.
  - Medicine, Department of, Staff Meeting with Pres. O'Neill February 1999, [n.d.], 2 TMemo, 13 TLS, 4 TD (Box-folder 033-001)
    Re: Hook solicits evaluations from department heads about the department of medicine.
  - Medicine, School of - 1971 Correspondence March-October 1971, 1 TMemo, 11 TLS, 10 TL, 2 TN (Box-folder 033-002)
    Re: Correspondence with the Office of the dean with Acting Director, Dr. James T. Hamlin.
  - Medicine, School of-- January-November 1972, 23 TL, 7 TLS, 2 TN, 1 TMemoS, 1 TD (Box-folder 033-003)
    Re: 1972 Correspondence between Hook & the Dean of the Medical School.
  - Morning Report May 1977-October 1984, 2 TMemo, TLS, 1 TL (Box-folder 033-004)
    Re: Discussion about format/structure of morning report.
  - Neurology September 1970-February 1986, 16 TL, 23 TLS, 4 TMemo, 1 AD, 1 AL, 1 TD (Box-folder 033-005)
    Re: Discussion about combining neurological & neurosurgical service, patient cases, seeing Towers patients in the tower building, C-T program, and hiring personnel.
  - Neurology December 1988-May 1990, 31 TLS, 1 TL, 1 TMemo, 3 ALS, 7 TD (Box-folder 033-006)
    Re: Northridge facility.
  - Neurology December 1970-November 1989, 28 TLS, 12 TL, 5 TMemo, 1 TD, 2 AD (Box-folder 033-007)
    Re: Correspondence primarily with John Jane, Chairman, Department of Neurological Surgery; discussion includes patient cases and medical student's training.
  - NMR Task Force June 1982-May 1985, 1 TN, 11 TLS, 4 TL (Box-folder 033-008)
    Re: Nuclear Magnetic Resonance.
  - Nursing, School of June 1982-June 1990, 18 TLS, 1 TL, 1 TMemo, 1 TD (Box-folder 033-009)
    Re: Teaching sessions for nursing students.
  - Nursing Service Correspondence September 1981-October 1982, 10 TLS, 2 TD, 9 TL, 2 TMs, 5 TMemo, 1 ANS, 1 ALS (Box-folder 033-010)
    Re: Bed closure in Barringer, discussion over incorrect information in a brochure, nursing shortage and implications at UVa, and a report concerning the decentralization of the Department of Subsidiary Nursing.
  - Nursing Service Correspondence January-October 1985, 18 TLS, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 033-011)
    Re: Describes the difficulty in obtaining nursing staff for ICU and other units.
  - Nursing Services, Correspondence January 1987-February 1990, 18 TLS, 1 TMs, 1 TD, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 033-012)
    Re: Correspondence discusses nursing concerns, charting vital signs, appointments, patient care and a manuscript about the"Proposed University of Virginia Institute on Aging".
  - Nurse, week of October 1983-April 1990, 3 TL, 5 TLS, 2 ANS, 1 TD, 1 TNS, 1 ALS (Box-folder 033-013)
    Re: Hook acknowledges nursing staff during week of the nurse.
  - Obstetrics & Gynecology July 1976-September 1989, 2 TL, 12 TLS, 2 TD (Box-folder 033-014)
    Re: Misc. minor issues.
  - Organizational Culture Task Force August 1994-April 1995, 1 TLS, 5 TD, 10 TMemo, 2 TMs (Box-folder 033-015)
    Re: Meetings & memos regarding Hook's involvement on this task force. Included is the draft of "The Report of the Organizational Culture Task Force".
  - Orthopedics May 1972-December 1986, 8 TL, 10 TLS, 1 AN, 1 TD (Box-folder 033-016)
    Re: Correspondence with Warren G. Stamp, Chairman, Dept. of Orthopedics.
  - Patents December 1987-March 1988, 1 TMemo, 4 TLS (Box-folder 033-017)
    Re: Commercializing your Innovations.
  - Pathology, Dept. of, Correspondence July 1984-February 1990, 11 TLS, 1 TD, 1 TL (Box-folder 033-018)
    Re: Misc. pathology issues.
  - Department of Pediatrics April 1970-May 1990, 7 TMemo, 13 TL, 30 TLS, 5 TD, 1 brochure, 1 AN (Box-folder 033-019)
    Re: 20 years of correspondence about department of pediatrics; including dialogue on care for handicapped teenagers, patients with cystic fibrosis, pediatric cardiology, and Children's Rehabilitation Center. Correspondence primarily with Robert M. Blizzard, Chair of Dept. of Pediatrics.
  - Pediatrics, Adolescent Medicine Program September 1977-December 1980, 2 TL, 6 TLS, 1 TD, 1 TMemo, 1 TMs (Box-folder 033-020)
    Re: Report: "Development of an Adolescent Health Care Program at the University of Virginia Medical Center".
  - Personal, Hook January 1969-January 1975, 4 TLS, 1 TD, 1 TL (Box-folder 034-001)
    Re: Hook is offered the position of Professor & Chairman of the Department of Internal Medicine; TD is Hook's notes on discussion about Medical Service.
  - Personal Letters, Awards April 1969-June 1990, 22 TLS, 3 TD, 8 printed certificate, 2 printed cards, 2 printed programs, 1 ALS (Box-folder 034-002)
    Re: Brief biography about Hook, Hook's convocation address, and Hook's awards.
  - Hook, Personal notes July 1989-1998, 9 TD, 1 printed certificate, 1 TMemo, 2 licenses, 1 TMs (Box-folder 034-003)
    Re: Included are Hook's typed personal reflections about his tenure as Chairman, Internal Medicine, a write-up for Who's Who in America, and a manuscript, "Academic Practice and Clinical Research 1950s and 1960s".
  - Pharmacology December 1969-August 1987, 1 TMemo, 4 TL, 6 TLS, 1 TD (Box-folder 034-004)
    Re: Misc.
  - Physical Plant July 1986-March 1989, 3 TLS, 2 TMemo (Box-folder 034-005)
    Re: Building issues.
  - Physical Medicine & Rehab November 1987-October 1988, 2 TMemo, 1 TL, 2 TLS (Box-folder 034-006)
    Re: Appointments; closue physical therapy acute.
  - Physiology, Department of January 1971-August 1990, 4 TL, 8 TLS, 2 TD (Box-folder 034-007)
    Re: Mis.
  - Restricted Access February-October 1973, 3 TMs, 2 TMs w/AN, 10 TD, 1 chart, 4 AN, 1 TN w/AN, 3 TDS, 1 TD w/ AN, 1 TL, 1 TLS (Box-folder 034-008)
    Re: Hippa.
  - Practice Plan (New) 1990 January-February 1990, 3 TMs, 3 Charts, 2 TD, 5 TLS (Box-folder 034-009)
    Re: Hook disagrees with Dean Carey's proposal draft on a new practice plan regarding salaries.
  - Preventive Medicine June 1987-November 1989, 10 TLS, 3 TD (Box-folder 034-010)
    Re: Preventive medicine residency program.
  - Primary Care August 1979-July 1980, 6 TD, 1 article clipping, 3 TLS, 3 TMemo (Box-folder 034-011)
    Re: Building policy of primary care, opening of the clinic, evaluation, and coordinating council meetings.
  - Primary Care Forum November-December 1988, 1 TMemo, 1 AL, 1 TMs, 2 TLS (Box-folder 034-012)
    Re: Response to UVa School of Medicine to the State's need for more and better Primary Care physicians; included is the memo produced by primary care health forum.
  - Primary Care Practice May 1988-June 1990, 1 TMemo, 1 article photocopy (1st page only), 6 TLS, 1 TD (Box-folder 034-013)
    Re: Expanding training in primary care.
  - Primary Care - Rural Office Practice June 1987-November 1988, 6 TLS, 2 TMemo, 3 TD (Box-folder 034-014)
    Re: Faculty development project in clinical teaching.
  - UVA Clinic, Private Division Policy Committee March 1968-August 1973, 10 TLS, 20 TDS, 5 TMemo, 9 TL, 5 TD (Box-folder 034-015)
    Re: Policy Committee Meetings, financial practices.
  - UVA Clinic, Private Division Policy (cont.) January 1974-June 1976, 25 TDS, 3 TL, 3 TLS, 3 TMemo, 1 TMs (Box-folder 034-016)
    Re: Committee meetings, included manuscript "University of Virginia Clinic, Private Division Patient Billing System".
  - UVa Clinic Private Division Policy Committee (Cont.), 5 TMs, 2 TMemo, 4 AN, 5 TLS (Box-folder 035-001)
    Re: Name change of Private Clinic Building, manscript, "University Hospital, Third Floor; Private Clinics", by-laws of Private Clinic Division, and Medical Practice Plan, 1979.
  - Private Clinic Division, Mr. Thomas Nalley April 1970-April 1976, 2 TMemo, 10 TL, 5 TLS (Box-folder 035-002)
    Re: Financial concerns such as billing, fees, insurance and appointment of director.
  - Private Clinic Division 1968-November 1978, [n.d.], 20 TD, 1 TMs, 1 Graph, 5 TMemo, 3 TL, 1 TLS (Box-folder 035-003)
    Re: Statements of Revenue and Expenses, and CPD Policy Committee meeting minutes.
  - Promotions October 1974-February 1988, 6 TL, 3 TMs, 19 TLS, 3 TMemo, 6 TD, 8 graphs, 1 AN (Box-folder 035-004)
    Re: Includes reports by Policy Committee on Promotions.
  - School of Medicine, Department of Psychiatry September 1969-August 1986, 4 TD, 11 TL, 18 TLS, 2 ALS, 2 TN, 3 TMemo (Box-folder 035-005)
    Re: Requirements for Psychology Students in '68-'69, discussion over admission of patients to Western State, sleep lab, staff additions and promotions, proposal for Division of Behavioral Medicine.
  - Pulmonary-correspondence 1970-1979, 21 TL, 19 TLS, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 035-006)
    Re: Financial issues, appointment of Dudley F. Rochester as Head of Pulmonary Medicine, pulmonary rotation at Salem Veteran's Adminstration Hospital, long range planning, use of iron lung.
  - Pulmonary - Correspondence 1980-1987, 2 TMs, 36 TLS, 16 TL, 2 TD, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 035-007)
    Re: Correspondence primarily with Dudley F. Rochester, Head Pulmonary-Allergy Division, Rochester's 1979 report "The Infectiousness of Tuberculosis: Guideline's for Policy at Blue Ridge Hospital", a 1986 "Proposal for Program Activity at Blue Ridge Hospital", recruitment of an allergist, space concerns, sleep apnea laboratory, bronchoscopy facilities.
  - Pulmonary-Correspondence 1990 July 1982-August 1989, 51 TLS, 1 TMemo, 6 TD (Box-folder 035-008)
    Re: Ventilator-dependent patients, development of Critical Care Program, long range financial support, research sleep disorder laboratory, MICU admissions policy, name change to Division of Pulmonary and Critical Medicine, lung transplants.
  - Pulmonary-Chronic Ventilator Care Unit September 1987-August 1989, 3 TD, 2 TMemo, 13 TLS (Box-folder 035-009)
    Re: Development of a unit to care for patients requiring long-term respiratory care.
  - Pulmonary-Sleep Laboratory April 1983-July 1986, 2 TMemo, 1 AMemo, 1 TN, 7 TLS, 1 TL, 1 TD, 1 TMs, 2 brochures (Box-folder 035-010)
    Re: Development of a sleep laboratory, includes project investigation report.
  - Radiology March 1970-September 1990, 57 TLS, 19 TL, 1 TD, 8 TMemo, 5 charts, 1 ALS, 1 ANS (Box-folder 036-001)
    Re: Billing, hours, residents, patient cases, and grand rounds.
  - Rehabilitation June 1986-January 1988, 3 TMemo, 17 TLS, 1 TD, 3 TL (Box-folder 036-002)
    Re: Expansion of Rehabilitation Services at Blue Ridge Hospital to include rehab and psychiatric facility, and an expanded alcohol & drug abuse facility.
  - Renovation Correspondence April-May 1984, 3 TMemo, 9 TD, 1 TLS (Box-folder 036-003)
    Re: Hook identifies areas for improvement in the physical areas of the department.
  - Renovation November 1969-April 1978, 50 TL, 19 TD, 1 Map, 8 TMemo, 33 TLS, 2 Estimate summary, 2 AN, 3 AL, 1 Newspaper clipping (Box-folder 036-004)
    Re: Hook deals with a multitude of space and laboratory demands; includes a 1970 proposal for Hook's office area renovation.
  - Renovations, East Wing Projections September-December 1976, 1 TMemo, 1 Survey & Statistics, 2 TMs, 1 TLS (Box-folder 036-005)
    RE: 1976 project needs and report to develop the East Wing of hospital.
  - Renovations, 4th Floor September 11, 1973, 1 TMs (Box-folder 036-006)
    Re: Department of Nursing and Medicine propose changes in the facility to better meet the needs of patients.
  - Renal September 1965-December 1981, [n.d.], 2 TMs, 5 TMemo, 17 TLS, 22 TL (Box-folder 036-007)
    Re: Correspondence primarily with Frederic B. Westervelt, Jr., project report from '65-'66, spacing and financial concerns of renal unit, dialysis fees, and staff positions.
  - Renal, Division of, correspondence October 1982-August 1987, 40 TLS, 2 TL, 3 TMemo (Box-folder 036-008)
    Re: Correspondence primarily with Frederic B. Westervelt, Division of Renal Medicine, transplant unit, patient cases, salary plans, dialysis services.
  - Renal November 1987-May 1990, 1 TL, 47 TLS, 5 TMemo, 1 AL, 1 AMemo, 8 TD, 1 Map (Box-folder 036-009)
    Re: Correspondence chiefly with W. Kline Bolton, Head, Division of Nephrology, department name change, vision for department, renal transplant program.
  - Renal: Primary Care Center Correspondence January 1980-December 1982, 1 TN, 38 TLS, 1 TMemo, 13 TL, 6 TD, 5 TMemo (Box-folder 037-001)
    Re: Establishing transplant unit, department meetings, renal laboratory, financial concerns, pediatric ICU, Luray Cavern's gift.
  - Renal, Primary Care Center, Correspondence 1983 October 1982-December 1983, 29 TLS, 9 TL, 2 TMemo, 2 TD (Box-folder 037-002)
    Re: Renal Chemistry Lab, bed allocations, sterilizing water supply.
  - Renal, Primary Care Center Correspondence 1986 April 1986-January 1987, 22 TLS, 2 TD, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 037-003)
    Re: Organ transplants, water sterilization, dialysis equipment, ambulatory dialysis facilities.
  - Replacement Hospital May 1986-May 1989, 11 TLS, 1 TL, 3 TD, 3 TMemo, 1 TMs (Box-folder 037-004)
    Re: Space usage in replacement Hospital, manuscript is the "Relocation Plan".
  - Research Report of Visiting Committee March-July 1981, 2 TMs, 5 TLS, 6 TMemo, 1 TD, 1 TL (Box-folder 037-005)
    Re: Manuscript "Report of the Visiting Committee on Research in Science to the University of Virginia, March 19-21, 1981" and "Research Portion of Institutional Self-Study."
  - Residents 1978-1989, [n.d.], 1 brochure, 5 TD (Box-folder 037-006)
    Re: Documents detail residents responsibilities.
  - Residents Clinical Competence September 1983-March 1989, 8 TMemo, 2 TD, 8 TLS (Box-folder 037-007)
    Re: Clinical Evaluation for Internal Medicine Board Examination and correspondence related to Committee on Clinical Competence.
  - Residents, elective February 1986-June 1989, 3 TMemo, 11 TLS, 1 TD (Box-folder 037-008)
    Re: Residents taking research electives in other divisions.
  - Residents, Numbers (Breakdown) January 1978-June 1984, 15 TLS, 6 TMemo, 14 TD, 1 TN, 6 TLS (Box-folder 037-009)
    Re:Statistice & information regarding residents.
  - Residents, correspondence February 1982-December 1988, 8 TD, 7 TMemo, 38 TLS, 3 TL (Box-folder 037-010)
    Re: Guidelines for Attending physicians, resident support system, appointments, resident workload, childcare for house staff.
  - Residents, correspondence (cont.) January 1989-April 1990, 30 TLS, 1 AL, 4 TD, 6 TMemo (Box-folder 037-011)
    Re: Electives, requirements for training, decline in student's interest (nationwide) in Internal Medicine, accreditation.
  - Respiratory Therapy July 1968-June 1986, 14 TLS, 6 TD, 1 TMemo, 2 TL, 1 ALS (Box-folder 037-012)
    Re: Prospectus for Respiratory Care Unit, 1968, Outline for protocol, purchase of equipment, respiratory inadequacies in MICU in 1980s.
  - Rheumatology July 1972-June 1985, 21 TLS, 13 TL, 5 TD, 1 AN, 1 TMs, 1 ALS (Box-folder 038-001)
    Re: Correspondence with John S. Davis, IV, head of the Division of Rheumatology, includes yearly status reports, finances, fellowships, staffing, report on the Arthritis Rehabilitation Unit.
  - Rheumatology (cont.) March 1986-June 1990, 45 TLS, 1 TL, 1 TD, 1 TMemo, 1 ALS (Box-folder 038-002)
    Re: Correspondence with John S. Davis, IV, head of the Division of Rheumatology, includes patient visits, faculty, patient care, Center for Arthritis and Lower Back Pain, yearly status reports.
  - School of Medicine, Associate Dean October 1972-May 1985, 26 TL, 5 TMemo, 6 TD, 18 TLS, 1 Invoice, 1 AN, 1 TNs (Box-folder 038-003)
    Re: Hook's correspondence with James W. Craig, M.D.
  - School of Medicine, Office of the Dean (1973) January 1973-January 1974, 1 ALS, 46 TL, 21 TLS, 2 TD, 3 TMemo (Box-folder 038-004)
    Re: Hook's 1973 correspondence with William R. Drucker, M.D.
  - School of Medicine, Office of the Dean (1974) January-December 1974, 43 TL, 1 TN, 6 TMemo, 28 TLS, 1 TMs, 1 TD (Box-folder 038-005)
    Re: Hook's 1974 correspondence with William R. Drucker, M.D.
  - School of Medicine, Office of the Dean (1975) November 1971-December 1975, 4 TN, 32 TLS, 46 TL, 7 TD, 1 AD, 1 Newspaper clipping (Box-folder 038-006)
    Re: Hook's 1975 correspondence with William R. Drucker, M.D.
  - School of Medicine, Office of the Dean (1976) January-December 1976, 30 TLS, 22 TL, 2 TMemo, 1 Invoice, 1 AN, 1 TD (Box-folder 038-007)
    Re: Hook's 1976 correspondence with William R. Drucker, M.D.
  - School of Medicine, Office of the Dean (1977) December 1976-December 1977, 43 TL, 23 TLS, 1 ALS, 10 TD, 1 TN, 1 TMemo (Box-folder 038-008)
    Re: Hook's 1977 correspondence with William R. Drucker, M.D. and his successor Norman J. Knorr, M.D.
  - School of Medicine, Office of the Dean (1978) January-December 1978, 30 TL, 12 TLS, 2 TN (Box-folder 038-009)
    Re: Hook's 1978 correspondence with Norman J. Knorr, M.D.
  - School of Medicine, Office of the Dean (1987-88) September 1987-September 1988, 27 TD, 9 TMemo, 6 TLS, 3 TL (Box-folder 039-001)
    Re: Hook's detailed notes on meetings with Robert M. Carey.
  - School of Medicine, Office of the Dean (1988-89) October 1988-April 1990, 38 TD, 1 TLS (Box-folder 039-002)
  - School of Medicine, Staffing Plan 1975, 1 TMs (Box-folder 039-003)
    Re: Hook is the chairman of the committee who wrote this report, "Staffing Plan: 1975-1980".
  - School of Medicine, Staffing Plan April 1971-July 1976, 5 TLS, 5 TD, 3 TMemo, 2 TMs, 3 TL, 1 AN (Box-folder 039-004)
    Re: Divisions within the Department of Internal Medicine make future projections, included is a 1976 Report by William R. Drucker, M.D. titled, "Academic Planning Schools of Medicine, University of Virginia".
  - Self-Study Report (Part I) February 1981, 1 TMs (Box-folder 039-005)
    Re: Comprehensive evaluation of the Department of Internal Medicine, 1981
  - Self-Study Report (Part II) February 1981, 1 TMs (Box-folder 039-006)
    Re: Evaluation of Resources and Programs, Department of Internal Medicine.
  - Staphcillin September 1960-1963, [n.d.], 3 brochures, 1 invitation, 1 program, 1 newspaper clipping, 6 TLS, 1 TN, 14 TD, 2 Invoice, 3 TLS, 1 Report form, 4 charts, 2 AD (Box-folder 040-001)
    Re: Hook's involvement in sensitivity testing for a new synthetic antibiotic, staphcillin.
  - Student Health March 1969-June 1983, 24 TL, 33 TLS, 3 TD, 1 TMs, 1 TN, 2 Articles, 1 TMs (Box-folder 040-002)
    Re: Hook's correspondence with the Director of Student Health, James L. Camp II, M.D. and his successor, Richard P. Keeling, M.D.
  - Students, correspondence September 1985-May 1990, 30 TLS, 4 TL, 4 TMemo, 1 TN, 1 ALS, 6 TD (Box-folder 040-003)
    Re: Hook's correspondence about student clerkships, evaluations, and test scores.